{
    "subject": "resource/Whitworth_University",
    "predicate": "ontology/type",
    "object": "resource/Private_university",
    "human_readable": "Whitworth University is a private university.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9790797233581543,
            "question": "Is Whitworth University public or private?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8026749491691589,
            "question": "What type of university is Whitworth University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6221323013305664,
            "question": "What is the cost of attending Whitworth University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.570968747138977,
            "question": "What is the size of Whitworth University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5677728652954102,
            "question": "Where is Whitworth University located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5627058148384094,
            "question": "Does Whitworth University have any notable alumni?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5417273044586182,
            "question": "Does Whitworth University offer any scholarships or financial aid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5119506120681763,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Whitworth University's academic programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4670090973377228,
            "question": "What are the admission requirements for Whitworth University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43898671865463257,
            "question": "What are some extracurricular activities available at Whitworth University?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Whitworth University is a private university.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5489_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the admission requirements for Whitworth University?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5489_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Whitworth University's academic programs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5489_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Whitworth University offer any scholarships or financial aid?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5489_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5489_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Whitworth University is a private Christian university, which supports the statement that it is a private university."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}